Hello friends, welcome to your
own channel The Retail Industry. Guys,
ICICI Lord General Insurance. Yes,
its quarter three numbers are out. The quarter numbers have come out just
10.15 minutes ago. How
were the numbers? What kind of numbers have they been? Let me take you
straight to the results. Friends, first of all,
remember that the numbers that are appearing in front of you are
in lax, so pay a
little attention. The plus printing is
absolutely rubbish.
Friends, let's discuss one by one.
First of all, let's look at the cross premium returns.
Okay, so in this there is
6436, you can say
643, sorry, this is after two points, so
6436 crores. These are looking so bad
that I don't know what to tell you.
6436 crores. Now, if you look at a year ago, it was
5599 crores and a quarter ago it was 61272
crores. So, brother, there is an increase in both quarter on quarter and year on
year. And
if you compare year on year,
you will see the same decent increase.
Coming to the net premium returns,  This
time it has earned Rs. 4690 crore which
was Rs. 4163 crore a year ago and Rs. 44240 crore a quarter ago. If we
talk about Premium
Earned Net, then it is Rs. 4304 crore which was Rs.
4300 crore a quarter ago and Rs.
3792 crore a quarter ago. Okay,
now let's talk about Income on
Investment, it is Rs. 665 crore which was Rs.
580 crore a quarter ago and Rs.
723 crore a quarter ago. Friends,
if you look at other income, here you will
see loss in foreign exchange, gain and loss, so
here it has been Rs. 1.25 crore which is
negligible, a year ago it was negative Rs. 22.6
crore. If you look at investment from pool, then
here you will see that it has been Rs. crore.
Okay, now when you add all these, then the
total income of the company which will come out is Rs.
553 crore, yes Rs. 5003 crore which if
you say a quarter ago
was Rs. 4362 crore and a quarter ago
friends, this was  5049 crores, so there is a quarter on
quarter decline, friends, year on year,
but if you look at it, an increase is clearly visible,
okay, but now let's look at the
expenses here, okay,
what kind of expenses have been the company's, so first of all, the
biggest expense has been commission
and brokerages of 845 crores, which you
can say was
174 crores a year ago, this time it is 845 crores
and a quarter ago it was 737 crores, okay,
net commission, if you look at friends,
if you find the net commission here, it is 845
crores, which was 737 crores a quarter ago
and 174.5 crores a year ago, okay, now let's
talk friends, what are the
operating expense related to
insurance, okay, in insurance business, the
first one is employer nomination, which is 312
crores, which was 27 crores a year ago, and
305 crores a year ago, okay, other
operating expenses, which include
advertising, sales promotion and others.
Look at the expenses,
in advertising publicity, you will see that the
expenditure has come down from Rs 146 crore to just Rs 38 crore,
which was Rs 42 crore a quarter ago. If
you look at sales promotion also, the
expenditure was Rs 577 crore a quarter ago, this
time it has come to just Rs 141 crore and there is no
premium deficiency. And when we add all these,
friends, what are the total expenses, you will find here, the
total expense here is 8, 9, 10, 11, okay,
and this is the net commission, friends,
brokerage and commission and net commission, both of these
are okay. Now you see what has come here,
friends, the total expense is coming here,
which was Rs 4587 crore a quarter ago,
okay, and
when you look at the unwritten profit and loss, friends, the
company has
incurred a loss of Rs 282 crore, which was
only Rs 145 crore a quarter ago. Quarter on
quarter, your loss has increased a lot, it has almost
doubled a year ago.  If it was 293 crores, then
you will see some decline in the loss,
but it is not so significant that
I would say that perhaps the
market may not like the numbers, friends. Okay,
now let's go a little down and see, if
you look at the company, what is the total
comprehensive total profit and loss
after tax,
friends, it came out to be 431 crores, okay, 431 crores,
which was only 352 crores a year ago and
577 crores a quarter ago, friends,
I am talking about profit and loss after tax,
okay. Now if you
look here, the company has given what you can call an
interim dividend, it is seen giving ₹ here,
friends,
okay. And when you look here,
see the company's total expenses, after the
provision for tax, if you add all these together, then your
profit and loss after tax
comes in positive, friends. Okay, so
these are the types of things because if you
look here, I will show you one thing,
one second you will find here that this is what we are
discussing here.  It was unrated
profit and loss, this was unwritten profit and loss,
then when we come to operating profit loss,
you go positive, okay here,
now let us go here and go down and
see friends, these things are
fine, so what kind of EPS has been their,
okay, EPS earnings per share, so
see where has your EPS gone,
friends, if you come to EPS here, it
jumped from ₹1 paisa to 87 paisa, yes, if you
look at it quarter by quarter, you might
see a decline, friends, now it has to be seen
that after the boom, how the market takes these numbers,
friends, yes, there has been an
increase in profit, but it has to be
seen how the market
takes it tomorrow, stay connected till here,
thank you very much, this is the end of this video,
Jai Hind